Guide to the Consumer Reports. Audiovisual materials, 1940-2011 and undated RL.11802
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Radio, 1969-1979; undated; 7
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 1, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-007)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 1, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-026)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 1, Undated (Box 73, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-066)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 1a, Undated (Box 73, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-068)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 1b, Undated (Box 73, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-067)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 2, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-009)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 2, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-025)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 3, 1969 Dec. 29 (Box 73, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-058)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 3, Undated (Box 32, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-006)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 3, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-010)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 3, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-024)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 4, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-023)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 4, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-033)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 5, Undated (Box 73, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-059)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 5, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-022)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 5, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-034)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 6, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-019)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 6, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-032)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 7, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-016)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 7, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-021)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 1, No. 7, Undated (Box 73, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-062)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 2, No. 2, Undated (Box 32, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-004)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 2, No. 2, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-030)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 2, No. 3, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-008)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 2, No. 3, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-020)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 2, No. 3, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-031)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 2, No. 3, Undated (Box 73, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-064)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 2, No. 4, Undated (Box 73, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-063)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 2, No. 4, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-011)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 2, No. 4, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-017)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 2, No. 5, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-012)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 2, No. 5, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-029)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 2, No. 6, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-013)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 2, No. 6, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-028)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 2, No. 6, Undated (Box 32, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-003)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 3, No. 1, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-014)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 3, No. 1, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-027)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 3, No. 2, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-015)
  - Report to Consumers Vol. 3, No. 2, Undated (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-018)
- Unidentified and Other Audiovisual Materials, 1957-2010; undated; 8
  - 2nd Rough Cut, 2002 Dec. 30 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-196)
  - 3 Sound Bites CA Couple, Undated (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0790)
  - A Day in The Life, 1998 Apr. 03 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0594)
  - Alan Bernhard Creative, 1991 Apr. 15 (Box 41, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-018)
  - Alex Haley #102, 1972 Nov. (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-049)
  - Alex Haley, Willa Baum, Tom Charlton #103, 1972 Nov. (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-050)
  - Anwar Fazal Interview pt #1, 2006 Aug. 20 (Box 67, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-079)
  - Anwar Fazal Interview pt #1, 2006 Aug. 20 (Box 67, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-080)
  - Anwar Fazal Interview pt #1, 2006 Aug. 20 (Box 67, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-081)
  - Anwar Fazal Interview pt #2, 2006 Aug. 20 (Box 67, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-082)
  - Anwar Fazal Interview pt #2, 2006 Aug. 20 (Box 67, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-083)
  - Anwar Fazal Interview pt #2, 2006 Aug. 20 (Box 67, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-084)
  - Bob Davis, 1962 (Box 63, Film-reel RL11802-F16-194)
  - Broken Glass, Undated (Box 17, Film-reel RL11802-F16-075)
  - Brom-Gordon, 1962 (Box 74, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-037)
  - CAC Meeting #68, 1973 June (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-047)
  - Cafe Screening, 2004 Feb./Mar. (Box 66, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0121)
  - Calalfo (Unsure of title spelling), 2003 Oct. 10 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1119)
  - Canadian Radio comm., 1965 Nov. (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-133)
  - CCI, 1962 (Box 74, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-031)
  - Charles Siepmann #67, 1972 Nov. 16 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-046)
  - Charlotte Rush, 2000 (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0178)
  - Consumer International Julian Edwards, Undated (Box 27, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0008)
  - Consumers Union Tape #2, 2001 Dec. 03 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-247)
  - Copy Tape #1 Into & Greenstein, 1986 Nov. 20 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-022)
  - Cromation for CU/CR, 2010 June 29 (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-063)
  - Dallas Devision Telecourse, Undated (Box 4, Film-reel RL11802-F16-038)
  - David DiH6, 1998 Sept. 29 (Box 99, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-218)
  - Differs From Finished Version in some Respects, Undated (Box 39, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-048)
  - DYG Conference 2000: Madelyn Hochstein - Social/Cultural Forces Shaping the Emerging Corporate Agenda (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0173)
  - DYG New York Conference 2001: Charles Kennedy III - Juggling Generations (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0174)
  - DYG New York Conference 2001: Daniel Yankelovich/Madelyn Hochstein (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0175)
  - Edit, 2003 Feb. 24 (Box 120, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-124)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt a Conversation (Xerox) #193, 1957 July (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-126)
  - Evening Magazine, Undated (Box 66, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0124)
  - Exhibit K, Undated (Box 120, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0473)
  - Eye on People A Day in the Life, 1998 Apr. 03 (Box 99, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0903)
  - Faye Henle's Dollars and Sense, 1963 Jan. 09 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-135)
  - FAZAL8.20.06_1_ (Box 67, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-071)
  - FAZAL8.20.06_2 (Box 67, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-072)
  - Fieldwork East, 2005 Feb. 07 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0756)
  - Fieldwork East Group 02, 2005 Feb. 07 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0763)
  - Fieldwork East Group 1-1, 2005 Feb. 07 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0762)
  - Fingerhail- Helen Chadwick, Undated (Box 72, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-013)
  - Flyer Printing, 2006 June 26 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0804)
  - Foo Gaik Sim MP3 Interview, 2006 Aug. 18 (Box 67, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-073)
  - Foo Gaik Sim MP3 Interview, 2006 Aug. 18 (Box 67, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-074)
  - Foo Gaik Sim MP3 Interview, 2006 Aug. 18 (Box 67, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-075)
  - Furman, 1969 (Box 76, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-079)
  - FXs for Florida Sail Boats, Undated (Box 72, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-010)
  - Gordon Hyatt-Resound of scene 9, 1973 June 12 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-123)
  - Guesswork, Undated (Box 60, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-106)
  - Herbert Denenberg University of Iowa, 1973 Oct. 13 (Box 111, Video-reel RL11802-RR-169)
  - Honeymoon in Vegas, 1992 Aug. 28 (Box 85, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-163)
  - Human Rights Watch, 2008 Nov. 04 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-353)
  - ICRT Summit, 2005 Oct. (Box 105, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-376)
  - ICRT Summit, 2005 Oct. (Box 105, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-377)
  - INT & Fury/Must, 1974 Mar./Apr. (Box 14, Film-reel RL11802-F8-009)
  - IOCU Council Meeting, 1965 Jan. 23 (Box 74, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-042)
  - JD PST Current Email (2) Archive Files, Undated (Box 120, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-394)
  - Jean Feraca, 1991 May 15 (Box 85, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-201)
  - Joe D----- 3rd week 4th week, Undated (Box 68, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-044)
  - Jupiter Communications Mindshare tape 1 of 2, 1999 Nov. 12 (Box 60, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0057)
  - Jupiter Communications Mindshare tape 2 of 2, 1999 Nov. 12 (Box 60, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0056)
  - Labels-With Filmstrips, Undated (Box 76, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-106)
  - Lebanon Relief No. 1 & 2, Undated (Box 5, Video-reel RL11802-Vid2-001)
  - les 400 couts, 2002 Mar. 7; 14 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0734)
  - les 400 couts, 2002 Mar. 7; 14 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0738)
  - les 400 couts, 2002 Mar. 7; 14 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0744)
  - Life Jaw-ETS at start - Head, Undated (Box 13, Film-reel RL11802-F16-019)
  - Like Family, 2003 Sept. 19 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0993)
  - Mai McQueen, 2003 May 26 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1161)
  - MAM Rumsey History of CP, Undated (Box 4, Film-reel RL11802-F16-035)
  - Mar-Beck ad, Undated (Box 105, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0389)
  - Martin Edelston, 1997 July 23 (Box 60, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0058)
  - Master Dub Startup, 1995 Aug. (Box 66, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0120)
  - Milwaukee Market; Tucson (Sierra Vista) Market, 2006 Mar. 15; 2006 Mar. 14 (Box 99, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0920)
  - Misc. 1, Undated (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0535)
  - Mitumi, Undated (Box 120, Disk RL11802-FD3-001)
  - MOD - Sandra Dowker, 1999 Feb. 18 (Box 99, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-231)
  - Mon PN, Undated (Box 120, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-221)
  - Moser R to C, Undated (Box 76, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-098)
  - Network Data, Undated (Box 120, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-395)
  - New Zealand #69, 1973 July 19 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-048)
  - No Title, Undated (Box 5, Film-reel RL11802-F16-053)
  - No Title, Undated (Box 28, Film-reel RL11802-F16-123)
  - Noticiero 47, 2001 Apr. 12 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0662)
  - PARROTS: Look Who's Talking, Undated (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0524)
  - Paul Reynolds, 1995 May 23 (Box 68, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0083)
  - Penny Power Subscribers and Expirees #250a, 19-- Nov. 04 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-157)
  - Penny Power Subscribers and Expirees #250b, 19-- Nov. 04 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-158)
  - Planned Confusion, Undated (Box 72, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-009)
  - Pontiac Commercial, 2000 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0647)
  - Pre-inauguration, 2001 Jan. (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0682)
  - Prescription Drug Commercials, Undated (Box 83, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0466)
  - Protest! A History of the American Consumer Movement, 1984 June 05 (Box 43, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-118)
  - Pure Oxygen #256, 2001 May 21 (Box 120, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0476)
  - Recap, Undated (Box 72, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-008)
  - Reel 1 #1, 1973 Aug. 10-11 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-142)
  - Reel 1 #2, 1973 Aug. 11 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-141)
  - Reel 1 #3, 1973 Aug. 12 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-143)
  - Reel 2, Undated (Box 2, Film-reel RL11802-F16-015)
  - Reference Tape, Undated (Box 87, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-182)
  - Richard Simpson, 1973 Oct. 13 (Box 111, Video-reel RL11802-RR-165)
  - Rick Paul, 2001 Mar. 19 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0673)
  - RL #7 VO #2 TC, 1985 Sept. 30 (Box 46, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-108)
  - Sales Film, 1975 (Box 20, Film-reel RL11802-F16-109)
  - Sound Roll #1, Undated (Box 72, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-012)
  - Special Libraries Association - 88th Annual Conference, 1997 (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0172)
  - Susan Siew Interview, 2006 Aug. 19 (Box 67, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-076)
  - Susan Siew Interview, 2006 Aug. 19 (Box 67, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-077)
  - Susan Siew Interview, 2006 Aug. 19 (Box 67, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-078)
  - Tape #18, 1986 Jan. 10 (Box 60, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-128)
  - Tape #3 Consumers Union, 2001 Dec. 03 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-248)
  - Tape #4 Consumers Union Jen, 2001 Dec. 03 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-249)
  - Telemarketers Find Alternatives for No Call List, 2003 July 10 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0700)
  - The Call Main St. Business, 2010 May 13 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-351)
  - The Call Main St. Business, 2010 May 13 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-352)
  - The Call Main St. Business, 2010 May 13 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-359)
  - The Call Main St. Business, 2010 May 13 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-360)
  - The New Challenges for Investigative Reporting, 2000 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0785)
  - The Power of Information, Undated (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0796)
  - The Power of PR in Branding: Best Practices in Defining, Supporting and Promoting Your Brand Disk 1, 2005 May 12 (Box 99, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-401)
  - The Power of PR in Branding: Best Practices in Defining, Supporting and Promoting Your Brand Disk 2, 2005 May 12 (Box 99, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-402)
  - The Slidell Story, 2003 (Box 61, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0066)
  - The Sopranos #1-4, Undated (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0530)
  - The Sopranos Episode 9-13, Undated (Box 85, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0550)
  - The Sopranos Episodes #5,6, Undated (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0511)
  - The Sopranos Episodes #7, 8, Undated (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0520)
  - The Wire 11 12, Undated (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0512)
  - The Wire 13, Undated (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0510)
  - The Wire Episode 9, 10, Undated (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0518)
  - Trans Atlantic Consumer Dialogue (TACD) Workshop, 2002 Oct. 31-Nov. 1 (Box 120, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-392)
  - Trans Atlantic Consumer Dialogue (TACD) Workshop, 2002 Oct. 32-Nov. 1 (Box 120, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-393)
  - Tricks of the Trade, 2001 Oct. (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0693)
  - Tricks of the Trade, 2003 Dec. 05 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0704)
  - Tricks of the Trade Follow Up, 2003 Dec. 12 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0705)
  - Trudy, Undated (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0668)
  - Untitled, 1962 (Box 74, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-028)
  - Untitled, 1962 (Box 74, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-029)
  - Untitled, 1962 (Box 74, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-030)
  - Untitled, 1962 (Box 74, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-032)
  - Untitled, 1962 (Box 74, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-038)
  - Untitled, 1962 (Box 74, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-039)
  - Untitled, 1962 (Box 74, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-040)
  - Untitled, 1962 (Box 74, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-041)
  - Untitled, 1973 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-145)
  - Untitled, 1974 Aug./Sept. (Box 14, Film-reel RL11802-F8-006)
  - Untitled, 1991 Sept. 12 (Box 99, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-239)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 56, Film-reel RL11802-F16-165)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-142)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 120, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-218)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 99, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-235)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 5, Film-reel RL11802-F16-050)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 14, Film-reel RL11802-F16-064)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 17, Film-reel RL11802-F16-073)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 70, Film-reel RL11802-F16-202)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 72, Film-reel RL11802-F8-030)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 137, Video-cassette RL11802-MDV-005)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 137, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-722)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 72, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-005)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 72, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-011)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 61, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0069)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 85, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0363)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 105, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0397)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0522)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0523)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0585)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0766)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0989)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0990)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0991)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0992)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 105, Video-cassette RL11802-VHSc-001)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 99, Disk RL11802-FD3-002)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 134, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-678)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 137, Disk RL11802-USB-001)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0771)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 99, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0934)
  - URL Racement, Undated (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-188)
  - Urvashi Rangan, 2002 Apr. 27 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1168)
  - V.O. Music, Undated (Box 64, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-142)
  - Vic Reinemer, 1973 Oct. 13 (Box 111, Video-reel RL11802-RR-171)
  - W.O.W. No. 31 Wastewise: A Community Resource Centre, 1991 Dec. (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0519)
  - Warner-Plimpton, 1962 (Box 74, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-035)
  - WCBS, 1996 Mar. 12 (Box 85, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-203)
  - Which? Power, 2005 Oct. 19 (Box 68, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-070)
  - Wild Narration, 1973 Aug. 14 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-132)
  - Won No. 31 Wastewise: A Community Resource Center:, 1991 Dec. (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0514)
  - zMax informercials, 1999 June 27 (Box 105, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0395)